Oh my god, this is the
kind of thing that makes you want to be bad,
okay, okay, all out.  The
flight was about to take off, and we
said in English, "All out, all right, excuse
me, please, please, let me go, symbol,
flight, [ __ ],
what are you doing, this eye is sore, left eye, over, don't worry, do
n't worry, why is this vomiting coming? What can I do? My eye is
vomiting coming. I opened the window, put my
head out, vomited, and I don't know
how to go to the bathroom.
This boy is sleeping somewhere else. I wonder if
all the lights are like that. This is where I
put the toy.
I think this is the bathroom. This is how I
scream.
What a beautiful sound is being made, what a
beautiful sound is being made, has someone come to the exit,
who is that crazy woman, has
someone come to the exit,
oh oh oh is that crazy woman?